We're going to stretch.
If you've got to be up here with it, be up here with it.
If it looks like this, that's cool too.
The whole point is can you feel it?
Can you feel it?
But the goal is to stretch in here.
So you're feeling this in your neck right now, right?
We're going to go back to this one more time.
Put that titty on your knee.
Put your hands on the back of your head.
You're stretching out the back of your neck.
We're going to move.
Feel this in your hips, your knees, your arms, your shoulders.
Wake that booty up.
Wake them hips up.
Ever so often, hit it with a dip.
Get all sides of that shit.
Butter that bread.
We're going to talk.
But we want to determine our own cycles.
We want to break out of the cycles that are determined for us by those who don't want us to win.